{
	"list": [{
			"quizid": "1",
			"title": "HTML",
			"description": "Quiz on HTML"
	},
	{
			"quizid": "2",
			"title": "Java",
			"description": "Quiz on Java"
	}],
	"data": [{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "100",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What does HTML stand for?",
			"answerChoices": ["Hypertext Markup Language",
				"Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
				"Head Text Marked Language",
				"Hypertext Modified Language"],
			"meta":{
	      "next_question": "101"
			}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "101",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the largest heading in HTML?",
			"answerChoices": ["<h6>",
				"<h1>",
				"<heading>",
				"head"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "102"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "102",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which tag is used to create an ordered list?",
			"answerChoices": ["<ol>",
				"<ul>",
				"<li>",
				"<a>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "103"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "103",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "Type in below the correct tag for creating a hyperlink",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "104"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "104",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the correct way to create a table",
			"answerChoices": ["<td>",
			 "<t>",
			 "<table>",
			 "<tr>"],
	    "meta":{
	    	"next_question": "105"
	    }
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "105",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which tag is used for adding videos to a website?",
			"answerChoices": ["<video>",
				"<media>",
				"<vid>",
				"<movie>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "106"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "106",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "How is a HTML5 document initialized?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "107"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "107",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which tag is used for adding sound to a website?",
			"answerChoices": ["<sound>",
				"<media>",
				"<audio>",
				"<mp3>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "108"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "108",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the correct way to make the text bold?",
			"answerChoices": ["<imp>",
				"<bold>",
				"<em>",
				"<b>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "109"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "109",
			"type": "tF",
			"q": "/ is the character that is used to close a tag?",
			"answerChoices": ["True",
				 "False"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "110"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "110",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What HTML element is used to inserting a line break?",
			"answerChoices": ["<break>",
				"<br>",
				"<brake>",
				"<line>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "111"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "111",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the HTML element used for creating a bullet list?",
			"answerChoices": ["<list>",
				"<bl>",
				"<ul>",
				"<li>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "112"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "112",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "What HTML attribute is used to define inline-styles directly on HTML element?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "113"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "113",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "How can you add a comment in HTML?",
			"answerChoices": ["<!-- and -->",
				"//",
			  "/*",
				"comment"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "114"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "114",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Select the correct way to create a checkbox field.",
			"answerChoices": ["<input type=\"checkbox\">",
				"<input style=\"checkbox\">",
				"<input style=\"check\">",
				"<checkbox>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "115"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "115",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "How many different headings are there?",
			"answerChoices": ["1",
				"6",
				"3",
				"4"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "116"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "116",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Select the correct HTML syntax for creating a text input.",
			"answerChoices": ["<input type=\"text\">",
				"<textfield>",
				"<input type=\"textfield\">",
				"<input style=\"text\">"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "117"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "117",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which is the correct way to set a background color for the HTML page?",
			"answerChoices": ["<body bg='yellow'>",
				"<body style=\"background-color:blue\">",
				"<background setColor:red>",
				"<body green>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "118"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "118",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "Enter below the correct tag to use when implementing JavaScript in HTML.",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "119"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "119",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which is the correct way to put a picture on the HTML page?",
			"answerChoices": ["<media>",
				"<image>",
				"<pic>",
				"<img>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "-1"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "200",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "Type in the correct method to output something in Java?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "201"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "201",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the correct data type to store text?",
			"answerChoices": ["String",
				"string",
				"str",
				"Text"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "202"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "202",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which is the correct way to declare an array?",
			"answerChoices": ["<>",
				"()",
				"{}",
				"[]"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "203"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "203",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which variable is used to store integers?",
			"answerChoices": ["i",
				"int",
				"String",
				"boolean"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "204"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "204",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is another way of writing the notation x=x+2",
			"answerChoices": ["y=x-2",
				"x=y-2",
				"x+=2",
				"x-=2"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "205"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "205",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "What keyword is used to return a value in a method?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "206"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "206",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "What keyword is used to stop a loop?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "207"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "207",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is import used for?",
			"answerChoices": ["To import a package from Java API library",
				"To import a method",
				"To import a variable",
				"To import an array"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "208"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "208",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "What operator is used to compare two numeric values?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "209"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "209",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What method is used to find the size of a String?",
			"answerChoices": ["length()",
				"String()",
				"size()",
				"getSize()"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "210"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "210",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the method .equals() used for?",
			"answerChoices": ["Compare String variables.",
				"To set a String to a variable",
				"To compare two operators",
				"To compare packages."],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "211"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "211",
			"type": "tR",
			"q": "What operator is used to add two values together?",
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "212"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "212",
			"type": "tF",
			"q": "upperCase() is the method used to return a String in upper case letters?",
			"answerChoices": ["True",
				"False"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "213"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "213",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Array indexes start with",
			"answerChoices": ["1",
				"0",
				"10",
				"2"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "214"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "214",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the correct way to create a method?",
			"answerChoices": ["(name)",
				"name[]",
				"name()",
				"<name>"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "215"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "215",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What operator is used to end each line of code?",
			"answerChoices": ["<",
				"/",
				">",
				";"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "216"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "216",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of myClass?",
			"answerChoices": ["myClass myObj=new myClass();",
				"class myClass=new myObject;",
				"new myObj=myClass();",
				"class myObj=new myClass();"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "217"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "217",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which method can be used to find the highest value between x and y?",
			"answerChoices": ["Math.maxNum(x,y)",
				"Math.max(x,y)",
				"Math.largest(x,y)",
				"Math.maximum(x,y)"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "218"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "218",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which operator is used to multiple numbers?",
			"answerChoices": ["x",
				"+",
				"*",
				"/"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "219"
    	}
		},

		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "219",
			"type": "mc",
			"q": "Which keyword keeps the main method from returning any value?",
			"answerChoices": ["restricted",
				"concealed",
				"void",
				"null"],
			"meta":{
        "next_question": "-1"
    }
		}

	],

		"answers": [{
			"quizid": "1",
			"id": "100",
			"answer": "Hypertext Markup Language",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "All the other acronyms do not exist, it is a markup language."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "101",
			"answer": "<h1>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Headings range from <h1> to <h6> the lower the number the more important the heading."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "102",
			"answer": "<ol>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<ol> stands for ordered list, <ul> is unordered list and <li> is used to list the items."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "103",
			"answer": "<a>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<a> is the main way to define a hyperlink."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "104",
			"answer": "<table>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<table> is the way to initiate a table and <t> is not a tag that exist. <td> is used to enter table data and <tr> is to define rows in the table."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "105",
			"answer": "<video>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "This was tricky, but <media>, <movie>, and <vid> doesn't exist as a tag."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "106",
			"answer": "<!DOCTYPE html>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Other tags like <html> is used to start a HTML file, but to initialize the entire document use <!DOCTYPE html>"
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "107",
			"answer": "<audio>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<media>, <sound>, <mp3> all doesn't exist."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "108",
			"answer": "<b>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<b> stands for bold, but <bold> is not a tag, while <em> is used to italicize words and <imp> doesn't exist."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "109",
			"answer": "True",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Use / to close a tag."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "110",
			"answer": "<br>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<br> is short for break."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "111",
			"answer": "<ul>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<ul> is an unordered list."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "112",
			"answer": "style",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Only use style to define styles in a HTML file."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "113",
			"answer": "<!-- and -->",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<!-- and --> is the way to leave a comment on HTML."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "114",
			"answer": "<input type=\"checkbox\">",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<input type=\"checkbox\"> is the correct way to create a checkbox field."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "115",
			"answer": "6",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Headings range from <h1> to <h6>."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "116",
			"answer": "<input type=\"text\">",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<input type=\"textfield\"> is the correct way."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "117",
			"answer": "<body style=\"background-color:blue\">",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "style=background-color is the correct way to set a background color for the HTML page."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "118",
			"answer": "<script>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<script> is correct way to implement JavaScript in the HTML file."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "1",
      "id": "119",
			"answer": "<img>",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "<img> is correct way to add pictures."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "200",
			"answer": "println()",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "println() displays the things that you are trying to print."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "201",
			"answer": "String",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "String is the correct way, make sure it the 'S' is capitalized. The uncapitlize is used in C++."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "202",
			"answer": "[]",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Arrays are declared with '[]', '()' are used in methods and '{}' are used for classes."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "203",
			"answer": "int",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "int is used for integers and String is used for collection of characters. Boolean is used for true or false."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "204",
			"answer": "x+=2",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "+= is used to add the variable with the value while the returned store as the variable."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "205",
			"answer": "return",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "return is used in a method to return the value."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "206",
			"answer": "break",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "break stops the loop."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "207",
			"answer": "To import a package from Java API library",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "import is used to access the Java API library and import it into the java file."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "208",
			"answer": "==",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "== is used to compare two numeric values."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "209",
			"answer": "length()",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "length() is used to return the size of the String."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "210",
			"answer": "Compare String variables.",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": ".equals() is used to compare two String instances."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "211",
			"answer": "+",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "+ is used to add."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "212",
			"answer": "False",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "toUpperCase() is the correct method to use."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "213",
			"answer": "0",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Array start at position 0 due to the off by one error."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "214",
			"answer": "name()",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "name() is the correct way to create a method, methodName[] would be an array."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "215",
			"answer": ";",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "; closes out each line of code."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "216",
			"answer": "myClass myObj=new myClass();",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Class goes first then object name and then call the class."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "217",
			"answer": "Math.max(x,y)",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "Math.max() is the correct method that is part of the default java library."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "218",
			"answer": "*",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "* is used to multiple numbers in Java not the traditional x."
		},
		{
			"quizid": "2",
      "id": "219",
			"answer": "void",
			"correct": "",
			"fb": "void is the only one that works in this case."
		}
	]
}
